Doll & Richards Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Financial Records, 1871-1973, bulk 1902-1969, Series 5:; (Boxes 18-69, 79, BV81-112; 55 linear feet)
  - Sales Records, circa 1883, 1901-1973, bulk 1902-1968, 5.2:
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 42)
      - Nos. B4,900-B4,999, March 24, 1909 - January 6, 1911 (Box 42, Folder 24)
      - Nos. B5,000-B5,098, January 18, 1911 - August 15, 1912 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 43)
      - Nos. B5,100-B5,199, September 25, 1912 - January 30, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Nos. B5,200-B5,299, February 2, 1914 - January 16, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Nos. B5,300-B5,399, January 16 - December 11, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Nos. B5,400-B5,499, December 13, 1915 - December 27, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Nos. B5,500-B5,599, December 11, 1916 - July 31, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Nos. B5,600-B5,699, August 8, 1917 - January 13, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Nos. B5,700-B5,799, January 11 - December 10, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Nos. B5,800-B5,899, December 11, 1919 - March 4, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Nos. B5,900-B5,999, March 4 - December 6, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 9)
      - Nos. B6,000-B6,099, December 7, 1921 - December 27, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Nos. B6,100-B6,199, January 3 - September 10, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 11)
      - Nos. B6,200-B6,299, September 15, 1923 - April 3, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      - Nos. B6,300-B6,399, April 3, 1924 - January 17, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Nos. B6,400-B6,499, January 19 - November 11, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      - Nos. B6,500-B6,599, November 11, 1925 - January 30, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      - Nos. B6,600-B6,699, February 1 - November 4, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 16)
      - Nos. B6,700-B6,799, November 5, 1926 - February 26, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Nos. B6,800-B6,899, March 7 - December 7, 1927 (Box 43, Folder 18)
      - Nos. B6,900-B6,968, December 9, 1927 - March 2, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      - Nos. B7,000-B7,099, April 7 - December 31, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      - Nos. B7,100-B7,199, December 31, 1928 - March 25, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Nos. B7,200-B7,299, March 25 - November 14, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 22)
      - Nos. B7,300-B7,399, November 16, 1929 - February 4, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 23)
      - Nos. B7,400-B7,499, February 11 - April 21, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 24)
      - Nos. B7,500-B7,599, April 26 - December 1, 1930 (Box 43, Folder 25)
      - Nos. B7,600-B7,699, December 1, 1930 - March 12, 1931 (Box 43, Folder 26)
      - Nos. B7,700-B7,799, March 12, 1931 - April 2, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 44)
      - Nos. B7,800-B7,899, April 2 - December 22, 1932 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Nos. B7,900-B7,999, December 22, 1932 - November 10, 1933 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Nos. B8,000-B8,099, November 13, 1933 - October 11, 1934 (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Nos. B8,100-B8,199, October 18, 1934 - March 1, 1935 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Nos. B8,200-B8,299, March 2 - November 15, 1935 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Nos. B8,300-B8,399, November 15, 1935 - April 7, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Nos. B8,400-B8,499, April 7 - November 28, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Nos. B8,500-B8,599, December 1, 1936 - May 8, 1937 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Nos. B8,600-B8,699, May 10, 1937 - March 4, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Nos. B8,700-B8,799, March 25 - October 13, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Nos. B8,800-B8,899, October 13-25, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Nos. B8,900-B8,999, October 24 - December 15, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Nos. B9,000-B9,099, December 15, 1938 - April 6, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Nos. B9,100-B9,199, April 6 - November 20, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Nos. B9,200-B9,299, November 20, 1939 - March 30, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Nos. B9,300-B9,399, March 30 - October 15, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Nos. B9,400-B9,499, October 15, 1940 - March 28, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 17)
      - Nos. B9,500-B9,599, March 28 - October 16, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Nos. B9,600-B9,699, October 16 - November 27, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - Nos. B9,700-B9,799, November 27, 1941 - May 2, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Nos. B9,800-B9,899, May 4, 1942 - March 26, 1943 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Nos. B9,900-B9,999, April 3, 1943 - February 5, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Nos. B10,000-B10,099, February 7 - November 13, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 23)
      - Nos. B10,100-B10,199, November 17, 1944 - June 7, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 45)
      - Nos. B10,200-B10,299, June 7, 1945 - March 22, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Nos. B10,300-B10,399, March 23, 1946 - January 10, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Nos. B10,400-B10,499, January 14 - November 13, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Nos. B10,500-B10,599, November 15, 1947 - August 4, 1948 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Nos. B10,600-B10,699, August 13, 1948 - April 7, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Nos. B10,700-B10,799, April 12, 1949 - February 17, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - Nos. B10,800-B10,899, February 18 - October 24, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - Nos. B10,900-B10,999, October 24, 1950 - May 21, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Nos. B11,000-B11,099, May 23 - December 7, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Nos. B11,100-B11,199, December 7, 1951 - June 11, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Nos. B11,200-B11,299, June 17, 1952 - March 23, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Nos. B11,300-B11,399, March 23, 1953 - April 12, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Nos. B11,400-B11,499, April 13 - December 31, 1954 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Nos. B11,500-B11,599, January 3 - June 30, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Nos. B11,600-B11,699, July 6, 1955 - February 16, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Nos. B11,700-B11,799, February 16 - December 10, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - Nos. B11,800-B11,899, December 10, 1956 - May 29, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - Nos. B11,900-B11,999, June 3, 1957 - March 26, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Nos. B12,000-B12,099, March 27, 1958 - February 16, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Nos. B12,100-B12,199, February 28 - November 18, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Nos. B12,200-B12,299, November 20, 1959 - June 6, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 46)
      - Nos. B12,300-B12,399, June 11, 1960 - March 9, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Nos. B12,400-B12,499, March 13 - December 30, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Nos. B12,500-B12,599, January 2 - November 27, 1962 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Nos. B12,600-B12,699, November 27, 1962 - October 23, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Nos. B12,700-B12,799, October 26, 1963 - April 6, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Nos. B12,800-B12,899, April 7 - July 28, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Nos. B12,900-B12,999, July 28 - November 25, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Nos. B13,000-B13,099, November 25, 1964 - January 21, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Nos. B13,100-B13,199, January 21 - April 2, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Nos. B13,200-B13,299, April 2 - June 11, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Nos. B13,300-B13,399, June 11 - October 26, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Nos. B13,400-B13,499, October 27 - December 11, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Nos. B13,500-B13,599, December 11, 1965 - February 28, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Nos. B13,600-B13,699, February 28 - April 27, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Nos. B13,700-B13,799, April 28 - July 14, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Nos. B13,800-B13,899, July 14 - October 27, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Nos. B13,900-B13,999, October 27, 1966 - January 20, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Nos. B14,000-B14,099, January 20 - May 2, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Nos. B14,100-B14,199, May 3 - September 6, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - Nos. B14,200-B14,299, September 7 - December 23, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 47)
      - Nos. B14,300-B14,399, December 26, 1967 - May 13, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Nos. B14,400-B14,499, May 14 - October 31, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Nos. B14,501-B14,599, November 11, 1968 - May 9, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Nos. B14,582-B14,641, March 19 - August 4, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Nos. B14,642-B14,700, August 4 - December 27, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Nos. B14,701-B14,761, December 27, 1969 - June 6, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Nos. B14,762-B14,819, June 12, 1970 - April 16, 1971 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Nos. B14,820-B14,876, April 16, 1971 - April 12, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Nos. [B]14,877-[B]14,919, April 15, 1972 - January 19, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C12,200-C12,299, March 10 - May 6, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C12,300-C12,399, May 7 - June 30, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C12,400-C12,499, June 30 - September 12, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C12,500-C12,599, September 12 - October 27, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C12,600-C12,699, October 28 - December 6, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C12,700-C12,799, December 6, 1902 - January 10, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C12,800-C12,899, January 10 - March 13, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C12,900-C12,999, March 12 - May 14, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C13,000-C13,099, May 12 - July 7, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C13,100-C13,199, July 8 - September 18, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C13,200-C13,299, September 19 - October 26, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C13,300-C13,399, October 26 - December 12, 1903 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C13,400-C13,499, December 4, 1903 - January 26, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C13,500-C13,599, January 26 - April 21, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C13,600-C13,699, April 22 - June 23, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C13,700-C13,799, June 23 - September 21, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 48)
      - Nos. C13,800-C13,899, September 21 - November 28, 1904 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C13,900-C13,999, November 28, 1904 - January 13, 1905 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C14,000-C14,099, January 13 - March 29, 1905 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C14,100-C14,199, March 30 - June 15, 1905 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C14,200-C14,299, June 15 - September 18, 1905 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C14,300-C14,399, September 19 - November 10, 1905 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C14,400-C14,499, November 10 - December 27, 1905 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C14,500-C14,599, December 28, 1905 - February 17, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C14,600-C14,699, February 17 - April 24, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C14,700-C14,799, April 24 - July 13, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C14,800-C14,899, July 16 - October 10, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C14,900-C14,999, October 10 - November 20, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C15,000-C15,099, November 20 - December 24, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C15,100-C15,199, December 24, 1906 - February 6, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C15,200-C15,299, February 8 - March 18, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C15,300-C15,399, March 18 - May 29, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C15,400-C15,499, May 31 - August 14, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C15,500-C15,599, August 15 - September 21, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C15,600-C15,699, September 23 - October 31, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C15,700-C15,799, October 31 - December 7, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C15,800-C15,899, December 7, 1907 - January 6, 1908 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C15,900-C15,999, January 4 - March 4, 1908 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C16,000-C16,099, March 4 - April 21, 1908 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C16,100-C16,199, April 21 - June 3, 1908 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C16,200-C16,299, June 3 - September 8, 1908 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 49)
      - Nos. C16,300-C16,399, September 8 - October 22, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C16,400-C16,499, October 24 - November 30, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C16,500-C16,599, November 30, 1908 - January 18, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C16,600-C16,699, January 18 - March 17, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C16,700-C16,799, March 18 - July 29, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C16,800-C16,899, August 2 - October 7, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C16,900-C16,999, October 8 - November 23, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C17,000-C17,099, November 23 - December 29, 1909 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C17,100-C17,199, December 30, 1909 - February 9, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C17,200-C17,299, February 10 - April 13, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C17,300-C17,399, April 13 - June 2, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C17,400-C17,499, June 3 - August 19, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C17,500-C17,599, August 29 - November 8, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C17,600-C17,699, November 8 - December 29, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C17,700-C17,798, December 30, 1910 - May 6, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C17,800-C17,899, May 9 - October 21, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C17,900-C17,999, October 20 - December 14, 1911 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C18,000-C18,099, December 14, 1911 - March 22, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C18,100-C18,199, March 22 - July 20, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C18,200-C18,299, July 22 - October 29, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C18,300-C18,399, October 29 - December 4, 1912 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C18,400-C18,499, December 4, 1912 - January 21, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C18,500-C18,599, January 22 - April 1, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C18,600-C18,699, April 2 - June 11, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C18,700-C18,799, June 11 - October 6, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C18,800-C18,899, October 6 - November 15, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 50)
      - Nos. C18,900-C18,999, November 15 - December 20, 1913 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C19,000-C19,099, December 20, 1913 - February 6, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C19,100-C19,199, February 7 - April 9, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C19,200-C19,299, April 10 - June 29, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C19,300-C19,399, June 30 - October 31, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C19,400-C19,499, October 31 - December 31, 1914 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C19,500-C19,599, December 31, 1914 - March 20, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C19,600-C19,699, March 20 - June 17, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C19,700-C19,799, June 16 - October 24, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C19,800-C19,899, October 27 - December 1, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C19,900-C19,999, December 5, 1915 - January 4, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C20,000-C20,099, January 4 - February 26, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C20,100-C20,199, February 26 - April 18, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C20,200-C20,299, April 20 - June 2, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C20,300-C20,399, June 2 - August 31, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C20,400-C20,499, August 31 - October 26, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C20,500-C20,599, October 27 - December 5, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C20,600-C20,699, December 5-26, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C20,700-C20,799, December 27, 1916 - January 19, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C20,800-C20,899, January 19 - February 7, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C20,900-C20,999, February 9 - March 12, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C21,000-C21,099, March 12 - April 13, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C21,100-C21,199, April 13 - June 6, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C21,200-C21,299, June 6 - September 17, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C21,300-C21,399, September 18 - November 14, 1917 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 51)
      - Nos. C21,400-C21,499, November 15, 1917 - January 11, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C21,500-C21,599, January 11 - March 27, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C21,600-C21,699, March 27 - May 29, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C21,700-C21,799, May 29 - September 3, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C21,800-C21,899, September 3 - November 21, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C21,900-C21,999, November 23 - December 23, 1918 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C22,000-C22,099, December 23, 1918 - February 13, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C22,100-C22,199, February 13 - April 18, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C22,200-C22,299, April 14 - June 6, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C22,300-C22,399, June 6 - August 15, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C22,400-C22,499, August 15 - October 25, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C22,500-C22,599, October 25 - December 15, 1919 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C22,600-C22,699, December 16, 1919 - January 9, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C22,700-C22,799, January 9-20, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C22,800-C22,899, January 20 - April 6, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C22,900-C22,998, April 6 - June 1, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C23,000-C23,099, June 2 - September 14, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C23,100-C23,199, September 20 - November 19, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C23,200-C23,299, November 20 - December 23, 1920 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C23,300-C23,399, December 23, 1920 - February 16, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C23,400-C23,499, February 17 - March 26, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C23,500-C23,599, March 28 - May 6, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C23,600-C23,699, May 6 - July 14, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C23,700-C23,799, July 14 - October 14, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C23,800-C23,899, October 14 - November 16, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C23,900-C23,999, November 12 - December 12, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 52)
      - Nos. C24,000-C24,099, December 12, 1921 - January 14, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C24,100-C24,199, January 16 - March 6, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C24,200-C24,299, March 7 - April 25, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C24,300-C24,399, April 25 - June 26, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C24,400-C24,499, June 24 - September 11, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C24,500-C24,599, September 11 - October 23, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C24,600-C24,699, October 23 - November 13, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C24,700-C24,799, November 14 - December 11, 1922 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C24,800-C24,899, December 11, 1922 - January 8, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C24,900-C24,999, January 6 - February 16, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C25,000-C25,099, February 13 - March 24, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C25,100-C25,199, March 24 - May 5, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C25,200-C25,299, May 5-31, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C25,300-C25,399, May 29 - July 6, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C25,400-C25,499, July 6 - September 18, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C25,500-C25,599, September 23 - October 25, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C25,600-C25,699, October 26 - December 1, 1923 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C25,700-C25,799, December 1, 1923 - January 19, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C25,800-C25,899, January 21 - March 17, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C25,900-C25,999, March 17 - May 15, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C26,000-C26,099, May 15 - July 1, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C26,100-C26,199, July 1 - August 25, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C26,200-C26,299, August 26 - November 17, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C26,300-C26,399, November 17 - December 17, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C26,400-C26,499, December 17, 1924 - January 16, 1925 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C26,500-C26,599, January 16 - March 14, 1925 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 53)
      - Nos. C26,600-C26,699, March 14 - April 29, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C26,700-C26,799, April 30 - June 22, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C26,800-C26,899, June 22 - September 2, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C26,900-C26,999, September 2 - November 16, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C27,000-C27,099, November 16, 1925 - January 6, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C27,100-C27,199, January 2 - March 12, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C27,200-C27,299, March 13 - May 18, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C27,300-C27,399, May 18 - September 1, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C27,400-C27,499, September 3 - November 17, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C27,500-C27,599, November 17, 1926 - January 7, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C27,600-C27,699, January 1-7, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C27,700-C27,799, 1927, January 1 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C27,800-C27,899, January 1 - February 16, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C27,900-C27,999, 1927, February 17 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C28,000-C28,099, January 18 - March 12, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C28,100-C28,199, 1927, February 17 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C28,200-C28,299, February 17 - April 25, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C28,300-C28,399, April 18-30, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C28,400-C28,499, April 30 - June 28, 1927; September 24 - October 2, 1928 (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C28,500-C28,599, June 28 - July 21, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C28,600-C28,699, July 21 - October 28, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Nos. C28,700-C28,799, October 29 - November 26, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Nos. C28,800-C28,899, November 26 - December 17, 1927 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - Nos. C28,900-C28,999, December 19, 1927 - January 9, 1928 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Nos. C29,000-C29,099, January 9 - February 20, 1928 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - Nos. C29,100-C29,199, February 21 - March 24, 1928 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 54)
      - Nos. C29,200-C29,299, March 26 - April 21, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Nos. C29,300-C29,399, April 23 - May 9, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Nos. C29,400-C29,499, May 9-26, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Nos. C29,500-C29,599, May 26 - July 10, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Nos. C29,600-C29,699, July 10 - August 27, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Nos. C29,700-C29,799, August 27 - October 10, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Nos. C29,800-C29,899, October 11 - November 20, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Nos. C29,900-C29,999, November 20 - December 10, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Nos. C30,000-C30,099, December 11-26, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Nos. C30,100-C30,199, December 26, 1928 - January 17, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Nos. C30,200-C30,299, January 17 - February 15, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Nos. C30,300-C30,399, February 15 - March 8, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Nos. C30,400-C30,499, March 8 - April 10, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Nos. C30,500-C30,599, April 10 - May 14, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Nos. C30,600-C30,699, May 14 - June 4, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Nos. C30,700-C30,799, June 5 - July 15, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Nos. C30,800-C30,899, July 15 - August 21, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Nos. C30,900-C30,999, August 22 - October 9, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Nos. C31,000-C31,099, October 9-25, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - Nos. C31,100-C31,199, October 26 - November 29, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - Nos. C31,200-C31,299, November 30 - December 14, 1929 (Box 54, Folder 21)